Guide to the Nelson Sullivan Video Collection 1976 - 1989 MSS 357
© 2012 Fales Library and Special Collections
Nelson Sullivan Video Collection
1976 - 1989
MSS 357
© 2012 Fales Library and Special Collections
12.0 linear feet
Nelson Sullivan (1948-1989) was a video artist who documented downtown New York City in the 1980s. The Nelson Sullivan Video Collection contains videorecordings of the city's art world and LGBT community as well as performances in clubs, house parties, and interactions with Sullivan's friends from 1976-1989.
Arrangement
The archivist preserved the original order of the video collection as donated by the estate of Nelson Sullivan. The series of videorecordings have not been chronologically or thematically rearranged.
Biographical/Historical Note
Nelson Sullivan (1948-1989) was a video artist who documented downtown New York City in the 1980s. Originally from South Carolina, Sullivan moved to Manhattan in the 1970s and began filming the city's art world and gay scene. He captured John Sex, Sylvia Miles, RuPaul, and other performers at downtown bars and nightclubs including Danceteria, the Limelight, Palladium, and the Pyramid Club. Sullivan also chronicled house parties at his apartment at 5 Ninth Avenue in the Meatpacking District, gallery openings, park and street festivals, conversations with taxi drivers, and the ruminations of his friends including fashion designer Alexis Del Lago and journalist Michael Musto on film. He recorded almost 2,000 hours of tape, at first using a VHS-loading camera and later an 8mm video camera. Sullivan's filmmaking is recognizable for its point of view transitions and its stream-of-consciousness narration. He also often pointed a wide-angle lens at his own face while filming to record his commentary on the people, performances, or events that he captured. Sullivan made films up until his death from a heart attack on July 4, 1989.
Sources:
The 5 Ninth Avenue Project
John Sanchez Interview with Dick Richards about Nelson Sullivan
Scope and Content
The Nelson Sullivan Video Collection is a collection of videorecordings made by video artist Nelson Sullivan (1948-1989). The collection consists of videotapes of the city's art world and LGBT community as well as performances in clubs, house parties, and interactions with Sullivan's friends. The videos cover the period 1976-1989.
The collection is comprised of 1 series:
Series I: Videorecordings contains 8 boxes of videorecordings made by Nelson Sullivan.
Conditions Governing Access
Open to researchers. Appointments are necessary for the use of manuscript and archival collections.
Some audiovisual items have not been preserved and therefore are currently unavailable to researchers.
Provenance
The Nelson Sullivan Video Collection was donated to Fales Library by the estate of Nelson Sullivan, overseen by Dick Richards, David Goldman, and Robert Coddington operating collectively as the 5 Ninth Avenue Project, in September 2012.
Related Material at Fales Library and Special Collections
April Palmieri Papers
Downtown Flyers and Invitations
Arias, Joey, 1955-; Charles, RuPaul, 1960-; Eichelberger, Ethyl, 1945-1990; Field, Patricia, 1941-; Gunn, Moses, 1929-1993; Haring, Keith; Lady Bunny; Miles, Sylvia, 1932-; Musto, Michael, 1955-; Nevelson, Louise; Rotello, Gabriel; Sex, John; Warhol, Andy, 1928-1987; Woodlawn, Holly; 8mm.; Downtown Collection.; DVDs.; Gay men |z United States.; Gays in popular culture.; Gays |x Political activity |z New York (State) |z New York.; Performance art |z New York (State) |z New York.; Queer theory.; Video recordings |x Social aspects.; Videocassettes.; Videotapes |x Preservation.
- Videorecordings, 1976 - 1988
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open to researchers. Appointments are necessary.
  Some audiovisual items have not been preserved and therefore are currently unavailable to researchers.
  - Ameri/cain Gothic, undated (Box 1, Media ID: 357.0001)
    Access DVD available by appointment only.
    Scope and Content
    Performers: Sylvia Miles and Moses Gunn
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note
    Original Format: VHS
  - Now Explosion at the Pyramid Club, November 16, 1983 (Box 1, Media ID: 357.0002)
  - Chelsea Hotel (tape #2), November 20, 1983 (Box 1, Media ID: 357.0003)
    Original Tape 2 (of 2)
  - Joshua at Darinka, June 13, 1986 (Box 1, Media ID: 357.0004)
  - Pizza a Go Go, October 10, 1984 (Box 1, Media ID: 357.0005)
    With: Michael Musto
  - Hollywood Hell #2, December 3, 1983 (Box 1, Media ID: 357.0006)
  - Nirvana / Limelight / East Village / Nirvana, Tabboo!, Pierre Le Marshe, Shazork, 8 fast, Round the Clock, April 1, 1986 (Box 1, Media ID: 357.0007)
  - Atlanta 1986, February 1986 (Box 1, Media ID: 357.0008)
    [1] -- Spencer Thorton videos, 2/2/1986 [2] -- Peek Sisters videos, 2/2/1986 [3] -- Larry Tee at Celebrity Club (Atlanta), 2/27/1986 [4] RuPaul at Weekends (Atlanta), 2/27/1986
  - RuPaul at Danceteria, October 12, 1984 (Box 1, Media ID: 357.0009)
  - Louise Nevelson at Guggenheim, March 5, 1986 (Box 1, Media ID: 357.0010)
  - Casanova by Ethyl Eichelberger, March 15, 1986 (Box 1, Media ID: 357.0011)
  - Chelsea Hotel (tape #1), November 20, 1983 (Box 1, Media ID: 357.0012)
    Original Tape 1 (of 2)
    Access DVD available by appointment only. Please request Part 1 and Part 2.
  - Hollywood Hell #1, undated (Box 1, Media ID: 357.0013)
  - Atlanta (2), February 28, 1986 (Box 1, Media ID: 357.0014)
    [1] -- Butthole Surfers at 688 (Atlanta), 2/28/1986 [2] -- David Goldman's party with Lahoma, Lurleen, James (Atlanta), 2/28/1986
  - Pompeii, Bye Bye Birdie, March 27, 1986 (Box 1, Media ID: 357.0015)
    [1] Pompeii at The Saint, 3/27/1986 [2] -- Bye Bye Birdie - Hapi Phace, 3/27/1986
  - Nelson's Birthday, March 16, 1986 (Box 1, Media ID: 357.0016)
    7A to Liz’s car to Brooklyn, Musto's, Albert's
  - Shazork at Zulu Lounge, Bunny + Dimetri at Southern Funk, 1986 (Box 1, Media ID: 357.0017)
    [1] -- Shazork at Zulu Lounge, [3/23/1986] [2] -- Bunny + Dimetri at Southern Funk, [5/1/1986]
  - Disney Show at Limelight, March 2, 1986 (Box 1, Media ID: 357.0018)
  - Brant and Rhonda's Wedding, October 9, 1985 (Box 1, Media ID: 357.0019)
  - The Must in Boston, undated (Box 1, Media ID: 357.0020)
  - Pat Field's Store, January [29], 1986 (Box 1, Media ID: 357.0021)
  - Bobby's Birthday Party, undated (Box 1, Media ID: 357.0022)
  - Fred's Limelight X-Mas 1985, December 26, 1985 (Box 1, Media ID: 357.0023)
    [1] -- Fred's Limelight X-Mas, 12/26/1985 [2] -- Karen Bahari + Edwige - Area, 12/27/1985 [3] -- Stephanie Crawford at Pyramid, 12/27/1985
  - Buster Pointdexter at Limelight, November 19, 1985 (Box 1, Media ID: 357.0024)
  - Cocktail Girlz in Atlanta 688, Macrh 1, 1986 (Box 1, Media ID: 357.0025)
    Currently there is no access to this title. Please contact Fales Library.
  - Provincetown Wednesday and Thursday, August 1984 (Box 1, Media ID: 357.0026)
    [1] -- (P-town) Wednesday, 8/29/1984 [2] -- (P-town) Thursday, 8/30/1984
  - Provincetown, Massachusetts, August 1984 (Box 1, Media ID: 357.0027)
    [1] -- (P-town) Sylvia Miles, Richard Merrill, Bob Haas, 8/27/1984 [2] -- (P-town) Sylvia Miles, Richard Merrill, Bob Haas 8/28/1984
  - Michael Musto's Birthday #1, December 18, 1985 (Box 1, Media ID: 357.0028)
  - Beyond the Valley of La Cage at Limelight, December 17, 1985 (Box 1, Media ID: 357.0029)
  - Shazork at Pyramid, High Heels Women (La Mama), May 12, 1986 (Box 1, Media ID: 357.0030)
  - Shazork at Danceteria, David Chicklet's 10th Birthday at Limelight, Shazork at Pyramid, Pyramid, December 1985 (Box 2, Media ID: 357.0031)
    [1] -- Shazork at Danceteria, 12/6/1985 [2] -- David 10th Birthday at Limelight, 12/6/1985 [3] -- Shazork at Pyramid, 12/15/1985 [4] -- Pyramid, 12/15/1985
  - Joy Askew at Cat Club, January 14, 1986 (Box 2, Media ID: 357.0032)
  - New Year’s Eve at Pyramid with Love Delegation and Shazork #2, December 31, 1986 (Box 2, Media ID: 357.0033)
  - The Saint: Fashions for Japan, January 16, 1986 (Box 2, Media ID: 357.0034)
  - Michael Musto's Birthday #2, December 18, 1985 (Box 2, Media ID: 357.0035)
  - Fire Island, July 4, 1976 (Box 2, Media ID: 357.0036)
  - New Year’s Eve at Pyramid with Michael London and 3 TEENS KILL 4, December 31, 1986 (Box 2, Media ID: 357.0037)
  - 5 Ninth Ave Backyard (with Bob, Albert, Gaga, Maison, Johnny and the Pets), undated (Box 2, Media ID: 357.0038)
  - 5 Ninth Avenue (with Douglas and tour of apartment), undated (Box 2, Media ID: 357.0039)
  - Gabriel Rotello’s Eclectic Circus at Limelight, March 10, 1986 (Box 2, Media ID: 357.0040)
  - Downtown Divas I at Limelight, April 9, 1985 (Box 2, Media ID: 357.0041)
  - Shazork at Pyramid, Phoebe Legere at Limelight, February 9, 1986 (Box 2, Media ID: 357.0042)
  - Pop Tarts at Danceteria, December 15, 1986 (Box 2, Media ID: 357.0043)
  - The Sound of Muzak, April 21, 1986 (Box 2, Media ID: 357.0044)
  - Sylvia Miles Screen Test, Brant’s Music Video, undated (Box 2, Media ID: 357.0045)
  - Dinah Prince at Limelight, June 2, 1986 (Box 2, Media ID: 357.0046)
  - Gaylord, Alexis, John Sex, Joey Arias at Limelight, February 2, 1986 (Box 2, Media ID: 357.0047)
  - Cookie Watkins and Company at Cat Club, February 18, 1986 (Box 2, Media ID: 357.0048)
  - Ethyl Eichelberger in Leer and Casanova at Performing Garage, March 8, 1986 (Box 2, Media ID: 357.0049)
  - Follies at Cat Club, Walking Blackout (late night), Pyramid, [March 13, 1986] (Box 2, Media ID: 357.0050)
  - Cruel Story of Youth at The Dive, March 13, 1986 (Box 2, Media ID: 357.0051)
  - Bowling with Eric Conrad, TishGervaise at Danceteria, February 1986 (Box 2, Media ID: 357.0052)
    [1] -- Bowling with Eric Conrad, 2/14/1986 [2] -- TishGervaise at Danceteria, 2/22/1986
  - Gaga’s going away in Manhattan Plaza (with Eric, Morgan, Elmer, Jimmie), [May 7,] 1986 (Box 2, Media ID: 357.0053)
  - Michael Musto and John Sex at Palladium, John Sex at The Saint, 1986 (Box 2, Media ID: 357.0054)
    [1] -- Michael Musto at Palladium [2] -- John Sex at Palladium, 3/28/1986 [3] -- John Sex at The Saint, 4/4/1986
  - Patricia Field’s Hat Party at Area, October 28, 1985 (Box 2, Media ID: 357.0055)
  - Now Explosion at Danceteria, January 26, 1985 (Box 2, Media ID: 357.0056)
  - Albert Crudo at Danceteria, July 18, 1985 (Box 2, Media ID: 357.0057)
  - Now Explosion at Pyramid, January 25, 1985 (Box 2, Media ID: 357.0058)
  - 4th July with Rhonda and fireworks show on East River, July 4, 1983 (Box 2, Media ID: 357.0059)
  - Holly Woodlawn’s Park Avenue Party (tape #1), October 26, 1985 (Box 2, Media ID: 357.0060)
  - Ethyl Eichelberger’s Fowl Ball at Pyramid, November 9, 1985 (Box 3, Media ID: 357.0061)
  - Pop Tarts with Bunny, Love Delegation at Cat Club, September 25, 1985 (Box 3, Media ID: 357.0062)
  - Holly Woodlawn’s Park Avenue Party #2, Bunny at Danceteria, October 26, 1985 (Box 3, Media ID: 357.0063)
  - Emo Boutique Opening, November 19, 1985 (Box 3, Media ID: 357.0064)
  - Alexis Jungle Gardenia at Cat Club, John Sex at Limelight, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Media ID: 357.0065)
    [1] -- Alexis Jungle Gardenia at Cat Club, 10/21/1985 [2] -- John Sex at Limelight, 1/5/1986
  - Now Explosion at Pyramid (after the show), December 21, 1985 (Box 3, Media ID: 357.0066)
    Includes: Pyramid dressing room, van, and Nightbirds.
  - Now Explosion at Pyramid, December 21, 1985 (Box 3, Media ID: 357.0067)
  - Pop Tarts, Dean Johnson at Limelight, November 17, 1985 (Box 3, Media ID: 357.0068)
  - Holly Woodlawn's Birthday at Limelight, October 1, 1985 (Box 3, Media ID: 357.0069)
  - Jill Lynne Opening, Mark-on-Hudson, November 11, 1985 (Box 3, Media ID: 357.0070)
  - Fred R-M’s Birthday at Caroline’s, Vito's Awards at Limelight, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Media ID: 357.0071)
    [1] -- Fred R-M's Birthday at Caroline's, 10/8/1985 [2] -- Vito's Awards at Limelight, 1/9/1986
  - Pyramid with Tanya Ransom, Kennon Raines, 3 Teens Kill 4, September 5, 1985 (Box 3, Media ID: 357.0072)
  - Taboo at Pyramid, October 10, 1985 (Box 3, Media ID: 357.0073)
  - Andy Anderson’s Birthday at Tish’s, October 12, 1985 (Box 3, Media ID: 357.0074)
  - John Epperson (Lypsinka) at Pyramid, October 20, 1985 (Box 3, Media ID: 357.0075)
    Featuring: Billy Gallo, Mary K., Bobby S.
  - Tish’s TV Star Search at Limelight, August 28, 1985 (Box 3, Media ID: 357.0076)
  - New Music Seminar-Friday at Hotel with Now Explosion and Bunny, undated (Box 3, Media ID: 357.0077)
  - New Music Seminar-Saturday at Hotel, September 28, 1985 (Box 3, Media ID: 357.0078)
  - New Music Seminar-Thursday at Hotel, September 26, 1985 (Box 3, Media ID: 357.0079)
  - New Music Seminar-Saturday, Now Explosion at Pyramid, September 28, 1985 (Box 3, Media ID: 357.0080)
  - New Music Seminar-Sunday, Pyramid with Rosie, Lizette, Lahoma, Larry Tee, and Bunny, September 29, 1985 (Box 3, Media ID: 357.0081)
  - New Music Seminar-Friday with hurricane at Hotel, September 27, 1985 (Box 3, Media ID: 357.0082)
  - Downtown Dukes with Sylvain Sylvain at Limelight, July 1, 1985 (Box 3, Media ID: 357.0083)
  - Vito Bruno Boat Party, June 18, 1986 (Box 3, Media ID: 357.0084)
  - Downtown Dukes II with Holly Woodlawn as emcee at Limelight, September 17, 1985 (Box 3, Media ID: 357.0085)
    Cast List: Holly Woodlawn (emcee) 1) Michael Musto - I Want U Back 2) Hoy Boy 3) Pop Tarts 4) Dear Johns 5) Ned Sublette 6) John Collins 7) Zette 8) Randy Jones 9) Emanem [Johns] 10) [Sylva. Sylver] 11) Earl [Scoote] 12) David Johansen
  - Vito Bruno Downtown Awards at Limelight, Outlaw Party at Boat Basin, 1986 (Box 3, Media ID: 357.0086)
    [1] -- Vito Bruno Downtown Awards at Limelight, 1/9/1986 [2] -- Outlaw Party at Boat Basin, 5/15/1986
  - Vito Bruno's Outlaw Parties, 1985 (Box 3, Media ID: 357.0087)
    [1] -- Outlaw Party/Williamsburg Bridge, 6/6/1985 [2] -- Halloween, 1985
  - Boston, Whales in Boston, 1985 (Box 3, Media ID: 357.0088)
    [1] -- Boston, 7/7/1985 [2] -- Whales in Boston, 7/11/1985
  - Andy Warhol at Fiorucci, February 14, 1986 (Box 3, Media ID: 357.0090)
  - Duet or Die at Limelight, November 26, 1985 (Box 3, Media ID: 357.0091)
  - Gabriel Rotello's Downtown Divas and Dukes at Limelight, January 13, 1986 (Box 3, Media ID: 357.0092)
  - Mama Said Beauty Shop Sequences #3, undated (Box 4, Media ID: 357.0093)
  - Wendy Wild at Cat Club, August 1985 (Box 4, Media ID: 357.0094)
    [1] -- Wendy Wilde at Cat Club, 8/5/1985 [2] -- Bansi Strip Death at Cat Club, 8/5/1985 [3] -- W.W. + Mad Violets at Pyramid, 8/8/1985
  - Brant and Rhonda’s Wedding, November 8, 1985 (Box 4, Media ID: 357.0095)
  - RuPaul Walk, July 28, 1984 (Box 4, Media ID: 357.0096)
  - Halloween 1985 copy, Parade, Vito’s Water Club; Pyramid (Box 4, Media ID: 357.0097)
  - Peter Pan at Danceteria, December 12, 1983 (Box 4, Media ID: 357.0098)
  - Downtown Dukes and Divas First Anniversary, February 9, 1986 (Box 4, Media ID: 357.0099)
  - RuPaul Mix, July 10, 1986 (Box 4, Media ID: 357.0100)
    RuPaul is Starbooty Video Album, Terror I, Terror II, Terror 3-D, Star Booty The Movie, and much more
  - Mama Said Brunch, undated (Box 4, Media ID: 357.0101)
  - Madonna Impersonators at Pyramid, July 26, 1985 (Box 4, Media ID: 357.0102)
  - Christina at Danceteria, February 1, 1986 (Box 4, Media ID: 357.0103)
  - Liz and Albert Roof Party, undated (Box 4, Media ID: 357.0104)
  - Alexis Del Lago's Jungle Gardenia and Road Furrier (with Hapi Phace & Philly) at Pyramid, August 4, 1985 (Box 4, Media ID: 357.0105)
  - WHISPERS at Pyramid, August 11, 1985 (Box 4, Media ID: 357.0106)
    Sunday with Hapi, Loretta, Rosie, Bunny, Ethyl, Kennon, Wendy, etc.
  - Noh versus Musto - Trivial Pursuit on Nelson’s Roof, August 3, 1985 (Box 4, Media ID: 357.0107)
  - Halloween 1985, October 31, 1985 (Box 4, Media ID: 357.0108)
    Features: Parade, Vito's, Water C., and Pyramid
  - Mama Said Inserts, undated (Box 4, Media ID: 357.0109)
  - Vito Bruno Party Mix of Events, undated (Box 4, Media ID: 357.0110)
    O-Party Mix 2425 - Now Explosion 2710 - John Sex 2900 - Now Explosion 3050 - RuPaul 3215 - Cocktail Girls 3340 - Bunny Chase 3620 - Kilpig 3980 - Cookie Watkins 4188 - Shazork 4380 - Mr. Fashion 4560 - Now Explosion 4800 - RuPaul 4960 - Now Explosion 5140 - Now Explosion 5250 - Times Square
  - Mama Said Unedited, undated (Box 4, Media ID: 357.0111)
  - Vito Bruno's Glamour + Gossip, Pizza a Go Go, August 1, 1984 (Box 4, Media ID: 357.0112)
  - Vito Bruno’s Musto at Pizza a Go Go with Street the Beat, October 10, 1984 (Box 4, Media ID: 357.0113)
  - Downtown Divas III at Limelight, August 12, 1985 (Box 4, Media ID: 357.0114)
    Featuring: Debbie Cole, Lisa [Koutoukos], Kristie Rose, Holly Woodlawn, [Tish] + Smoky, Cookie Watkins, Ula Hedwig, Cherry Vanilla
  - Jennifer’s East Village Wedding, July 28, 1985 (Box 4, Media ID: 357.0115)
  - City Harvest Benefit, October 16, 1985 (Box 4, Media ID: 357.0116)
  - Surf’s Up Studio 54, July 30, 1985 (Box 4, Media ID: 357.0117)
  - Halloween Dukes and Divas at Limelight, October 29, 1985 (Box 4, Media ID: 357.0118)
  - John Sex at Cat Club, Talk Show at Musto’s, July 29, 1985 (Box 4, Media ID: 357.0119)
  - The Gong Show at Limelight, September 19, 1985 (Box 4, Media ID: 357.0120)
  - Mama Said Music - Baby Kelly Sings, undated (Box 4, Media ID: 357.0121)
  - The Must at Limelight, September 10, 1985 (Box 4, Media ID: 357.0122)
  - The Clowns Rambozo at Pyramid, September 15, 1985 (Box 4, Media ID: 357.0123)
    Featuring: Allen, Happi, Philly, Tabboo, Sally Randall, John Sex, Dean Johnson, Pat Orozco, Brian Trey
  - Mama Said Beauty Show #2 Original, undated (Box 4, Media ID: 357.0124)
  - Mama Said Beauty Show #1 Original, undated (Box 4, Media ID: 357.0125)
  - Mama Said Copy of Original, undated (Box 5, Media ID: 357.0126)
  - Glamour + Gossip - Vito Bruno at Pizza a Go Go, August 7, 1985 (Box 5, Media ID: 357.0127)
  - VHS Dubs, undated (Box 5, Media ID: 357.0128)
  - Hamlette with Ethel Eichelberger, February 9, 1985 (Box 5, Media ID: 357.0129)
  - Mama Said Florida Inserts, undated (Box 5, Media ID: 357.0130)
  - Mix Tape: Copy of Joey Arias and Copy of Vito Mix, October 2, 1986 (Box 5, Media ID: 357.0131)
  - Miami Vice with Sylvia Miles as Guest Star, undated (Box 5, Media ID: 357.0132)
  - Blackout Takes a Walk; Blackout's Birthday Surprise; Nelson Home Movie, undated (Box 5, Media ID: 357.0133)
  - Eddie on Wall Street (Original Edit Copy), undated (Box 5, Media ID: 357.0134)
  - Bunny Chase Original, June 26, 1985 (Box 5, Media ID: 357.0135)
  - Kristie Rose at Limelight, October 16, 1985 (Box 5, Media ID: 357.0136)
  - Now Explosion at Pyramid, July 28, 1984 (Box 5, Media ID: 357.0137)
  - Alice in Boston, September 5, 1984 (Box 5, Media ID: 357.0138)
  - Family Outing, March 27, 1985 (Box 5, Media ID: 357.0139)
    Featuring: Albert, Rhonda, Nathan, and Summer
  - Cocktail Girlz at Pyramid, October 11, 1985 (Box 5, Media ID: 357.0140)
  - Glamour + Gossip with Beauregard Houston-Montgomery and Oliver at Pizza a Go Go, August 1, 1984 (Box 5, Media ID: 357.0141)
  - Sylvia Miles in Oh Dad, Poor Dad in Provincetown, August 25, 1984 (Box 5, Media ID: 357.0142)
  - Miss Margie at Lucky 7, February 26, 1985 (Box 5, Media ID: 357.0143)
  - Friday with Sylvia and Alice in Provincetwon, 1984 (Box 5, Media ID: 357.0144)
  - Saturday with Sylvia in Provincetown, 1984 (Box 5, Media ID: 357.0145)
  - Chip Duckett For Florida Only, 1989 (Box 5, Media ID: 357.0146)
    Do not copy or show in New York
  - Dean Johnson at Pyramid, September 21, 1985 (Box 5, Media ID: 357.0147)
  - The Ritz, February 14, 1985; Original Format: VHS (Box 5, Media ID: 357.0148)
  - Atlanta #1, August 16, 1983 (Box 5, Media ID: 357.0149)
  - Gaga’s Birthday, July 24, 1984 (Box 5, Media ID: 357.0150)
  - L + K Man - Original Edit Madame Rosa’s, September 6, 1986 (Box 5, Media ID: 357.0151)
  - Mama Said Artists, Pyramid Float, undated (Box 5, Media ID: 357.0152)
  - Gay Pride March 1983 (Box 5, Media ID: 357.0153)
  - Sylvia Miles - Sunday Night Closing of Play in Provincetown, 1984 (Box 5, Media ID: 357.0154)
  - James Dean Tribute at Limelight, September 24, 1985 (Box 5, Media ID: 357.0155)
    Featuring: Cherry Vanilla, Lina Koutrakos, Earl Scooter, and Cookie Watkins
  - Studio 54, October 9, 1984 (Box 5, Media ID: 357.0156)
  - Glamour + Gossip, Pizza a Go Go, August 7, 1985 (Box 5, Media ID: 357.0157)
  - The Saint Japan Fashion Show, January 16, 1986 (Box 5, Media ID: 357.0158)
    Copy of edit #1
  - Blackout Takes a Walk, Blackout's Birthday Surprise, undated (Box 6, Media ID: 357.0159)
  - Scene Queens at Palladium, April 24, 1986 (Box 6, Media ID: 357.0160)
  - Atlanta #3, August 1983 (Box 6, Media ID: 357.0161)
  - Atlanta #4, August 1983 (Box 6, Media ID: 357.0162)
  - Mahogony at Pyramid, May 3, 1984 (Box 6, Media ID: 357.0163)
  - Mewborns in New York, June 24, 1984 (Box 6, Media ID: 357.0164)
  - Sylvia Miles in Provincetown, August 25, 1984 (Box 6, Media ID: 357.0165)
  - Now Explosion with Kennon at Pyramid, June 23, 1985 (Box 6, Media ID: 357.0166)
    Featuring: Dick, Alan Mace, Brian, Isadora, and Angelo
  - Palladium to Nightbirds, May 15, 1985 (Box 6, Media ID: 357.0167)
    Featuring: Albert, Musto, Tish, Sandy D., Eric, and Bill L.
  - Pat Field Copy of Edit, undated (Box 6, Media ID: 357.0168)
  - Uptown Dukes and Divas at Limelight, April 27, 1986 (Box 6, Media ID: 357.0169)
  - Morning Walk with Blackout, Pyramid Dubs for Clayton, undated (Box 6, Media ID: 357.0170)
  - Cookie Watkins at Kenny’s Castaway, January 1, 1986 (Box 6, Media ID: 357.0171)
  - Gaylord’s 1939 World’s Fair and Limelight, May 4, 1986 (Box 6, Media ID: 357.0172)
  - RuPaul at Pyramid, July 27, 1984 (Box 6, Media ID: 357.0173)
  - Sylvia Miles in Oh Dad, Poor Dad in River Arts, Woodstock, July 29, 1984 (Box 6, Media ID: 357.0174)
  - Atlanta #2, August 17, 1983 (Box 6, Media ID: 357.0175)
  - Zette at Limelight, April 28, 1986 (Box 6, Media ID: 357.0176)
  - Alice: Boston to New York, July 12, 1985 (Box 6, Media ID: 357.0177)
  - Sunny Bak at Latin Quarter, August 26, 1985 (Box 6, Media ID: 357.0178)
  - Road trip to Atlanta with Dick Kershaw, December 22, 1984 (Box 6, Media ID: 357.0179)
  - The Musto Miracle, Easter 1985 (Box 6, Media ID: 357.0180)
  - Gilligan’s Pyramid, August 24, 1985 (Box 6, Media ID: 357.0181)
  - Kennon and Adam Purple at Garden of Eden, Hiro, 7-A, August 11, 1985 (Box 6, Media ID: 357.0182)
  - Downtown Divas II at Limelight, May 16, 1985 (Box 6, Media ID: 357.0183)
  - Atlanta and Kershaw Christmas, 1984 (Box 6, Media ID: 357.0184)
  - Mary Kaye and Bobby’s Party, May 1983 (Box 6, Media ID: 357.0185)
  - Bunny Hop at Studio 54, April 20, 1984 (Box 6, Media ID: 357.0186)
  - Jamie Deroy Greene Street, February 7, 1985 (Box 6, Media ID: 357.0187)
  - Now Explosion at Danceteria, November 18, 1983 (Box 6, Media ID: 357.0188)
  - Statue of Liberty with Toyo, undated (Box 6, Media ID: 357.0189)
  - The Musto Miracle Easter, 1985 (Box 6, Media ID: 357.0190)
  - Dean Johnson at The World, May 6, 1986 (Box 7, Media ID: 357.0191)
  - Vito’s Bridge Party for Annie Flanders, June 6, 1985 (Box 7, Media ID: 357.0192)
  - AIDS Benefit, undated (Box 7, Media ID: 357.0193)
  - Provincetown 1985 (Box 7, Media ID: 357.0194)
  - Tish’s “It’s My Party”, January 11, 1985 (Box 7, Media ID: 357.0195)
  - Tom Rubnitz and The Pop Tarts at Pyramid, July 28, 1985 (Box 7, Media ID: 357.0196)
  - Zora and Bill’s Wedding #2, June 9, 1985 (Box 7, Media ID: 357.0197)
  - Zora and Bill’s Wedding #1, June 9, 1985 (Box 7, Media ID: 357.0198)
  - Tish and The Pop Tarts at Danceteria, July 26, 1985 (Box 7, Media ID: 357.0200)
  - Philly and Richard Hoffman - Historica Pagentia Fashionista Absurdia at Pyramid, August 10, 1985 (Box 7, Media ID: 357.0201)
  - Now Explosion with Kennon and Her Snake, June 23, 1985 (Box 7, Media ID: 357.0202)
  - Now Explosion Big Pussy Show at Pyramid, June 21, 1985 (Box 7, Media ID: 357.0203)